hmsite.net 2009-05-19

# Free Web Hosting with PHP, MySQL, FTP, POP and CPanel | HMSite

> In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, HMSite Hosting Provider has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.
> 
> We advise all visitors and clients to read and understand our privacy policy, and to check it periodically for any updates or revisions. If you have any questions about the contents of our statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mailing: 
> 
> This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which HMSite Hosting Provider collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").
> 
> **Privacy**  
>  Users' privacy is very important to HMSite Hosting Provider. HMSite Hosting Provider is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to HMSite Hosting Provider. 
> 
> **The Information We Collect**  
>  HMSite Hosting Provider may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. HMSite Hosting Provider may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.
> 
> **How We Use Information**  
>  HMSite Hosting Provider may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by HMSite Hosting Provider and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with HMSite Hosting Provider and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. HMSite Hosting Provider may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of HMSite Hosting Provider, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will HMSite Hosting Provider's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists.
> 
> **Disclosure of Information**  
>  HMSite Hosting Provider may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of HMSite Hosting Provider's business.
> 
> **Maintenance of Information**  
>  Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.
> 
> **Questions**  
>  Users may direct questions concerning this statement by e-mail.  Users may elect not to receive solicitations from HMSite Hosting Provider or from trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners by letting us know.
